## Curriculum Vitae – Jonas Van de Vyver

Personal Information Jonas Van de Vyver Homepage / Contact jonas.vandevyver@gmail.com

Driven computer engineer with experience in modern (web) development. Broad technologi-

cal, and scientific background. Focused on quality and the user. Fast and eager learner, team player who communicates well, adaptive, hardworking, motivated, and constantly improving.

EXPERIENCE

## 2015 - Current: Full Stack Developer, Software Engineer

- Venture Spirit

Analyze and implement new functionalities for a web application of a young company, both in the back-end (Ruby on Rails, Node/Express) and front-end (Ember) with modern web technologies (SASS, Redis, ES6, webpack, ...). Testing and deploying the application using agile methodologies. Develop, improve and test gamification algorithms,

## 2013 - 2015: Technical Analyst, Application Engineer

- Belfius Insurance

(1) Building a new central insurance policy application, from back- to frontend. Together with a large team gathering the technical requirements from several parties, modelling a suitable back-end (J2EE, Spring/Hibernate) and building a proof-of-concept of the application. Write technical standards, train and coach offshore development teams. (2) Together with 2 other developers be responsible for an internal messaging and content platform. Modeled and implemented back-end (Ruby on Rails) and implemented front-end (Angular 1.x).

EDUCATION

MSc Applied Engineering (ing), Electronics and ICT, major in ICT KAHO Sint-Lieven - Ghent (2012–2013)

Thesis: A quantitative comparison between meta-heuristic scheduling algorithms

Erasmus exchange: Computer Science at the University of Nottingham

BSc Applied Engineering, Electronics and ICT, major in ICT  $\it{KAHO~Sint-Lieven}$  -  $\it{Ghent}~(2009–2012)$ 

Industriële Wetenschappen VTI Sint-Laurentius Lokeren (2002–2008)

Languages	Language	Reading	Speaking	Writing	Understanding
	Dutch (native)	5	5	5	5
	English	5	4	4	4
	French	3	3	2	3

Courses taken

 $\mathbf{Jun~2014} \to \mathbf{Jun~2014}$  SQL Workshop, advanced - Abis Training

 $\mathbf{Nov}\ \mathbf{2013} o \mathbf{Nov}\ \mathbf{2013}$  Functional Application Design - Abis Training

 $\mathbf{Sep}\ \mathbf{2013} \to \mathbf{Sep}\ \mathbf{2013}$  Mainframe Environment - HoGent

 $\mathbf{Jan~2008} \to \mathbf{Jun~2008}$  Operating Systems part II - PCVO Waas en Durme.

Sep  $2007 \rightarrow Dec \ 2007$  Operating Systems part I - PCVO Waas en Durme.

Projects

2016 → Current Developer and Administrator for cryptobeleggers

Slack Community (over 300 people) by and for blockchain and cryptocurrency
enthousiasts. For which I've developed the website (Node/Express, HTML,
SASS), a Slack Chatbot which interfaces with a crypto daemon (Node, RPC)
and maintain the VPS hosted on an AWS EC2 Instance.

2015 → Current Building Krypto

Webapplication to track cryptocurrency portfolios, real-time price updates based on public APIs. With Telegram chatbot integration. Built with Node/Express, Postgres, Redis, AngularJS (1.x). Source on gitlab, for the built in automated CI.

Computer Skills

Programming: Javascript (ES6/ECMA2015+), Ruby, Java, C, Rust

Web Application Frameworks: Ruby on Rails, Spring/Hibernate, Node/Express,

Meteor, Elixir

Front-End Frameworks: Angular JS(1.x), Angular (2), EmberJS, yarn/npm,

Webpack, Babel

Webdesign: HTML, CSS3, Sass

Database Systems: SQL, Postgresql, DB2, MongoDB

Version control : git, SVN

Building, Deploying, Monitoring: Chef, openshift, AWS, CircleCI, Datadog